Finding Aid for the Alfred H. Bartles Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- DETAILED CONTAINER LIST
  - Series D: Correspondence
    - Subseries 1: Non-Family and Professional
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional Folder (Box 27)
        - Collective: Alfred H. Bartles—Outgoing, multiple recipients (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - Collective: Cello Students/Parents’ Correspondence, Undated, 1962-1963, Aug. (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - Collective: Cello Students/Parents’ Correspondence, 1963, Oct.-1969 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - Collective: Cello Students/Parents’ Correspondence—ca. 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
          Content relates to cancer operation
        - A.G. Edwards and Sons (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 27, Folder 5)
          Chief correspondent: Bateman, Tom
        - Adam, Claus, Eleanor, and Hansi, Undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
        - Adam, Claus, Eleanor, and Hansi, 1954-1972 (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - Adam, Claus, Eleanor, and Hansi, 1981-1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
        - Adams, Byron, Jr. (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - Adamiak, [Frau] (Box 27, Folder 10)
        - Ahrendt, Karl and Chris—, 1963-1970 (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - Ahrendt, Karl and Chris—, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 12)
        - Ahrendt, Karl and Chris, 1975-1981 (Box 27, Folder 13)
        - Ahrendt, Karl and Chris, 1982-1991 (Box 27, Folder 14)
        - Alexandra, Marica[?] (Box 27, Folder 15)
        - Almitra Music Co., Inc. (Delevan, New York) (Box 27, Folder 16)
        - AlphaComp (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 27, Folder 17)
        - Altes Schauspielhaus (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 27, Folder 18)
        - American Federation of Musicians, Local 291 (Newburgh, New York) (Box 27, Folder 19)
        - American Federation of Musicians & Employers’ Pension Fund (Box 27, Folder 20)
        - American Music Center, Inc. (New York, New York) (Box 27, Folder 21)
        - American Society of Composers, Authors & Publishers (ASCAP) (Box 27, Folder 22)
        - American String Teachers Association (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Sketchbooks (Box 28)
        - Ames, Richard (Box 28, Folder 1)
        - Anderson, John and Nancy (Independence, Missouri) (Box 28, Folder 2)
        - André, Maurice (Box 28, Folder 3)
        - Anthroposophic Press (Box 28, Folder 4)
        - Anthroposophical Newsletter (Spring Valley, New York) (Box 28, Folder 5)
        - Anthroposophical Society in America (New York, New York) (Box 28, Folder 6)
        - Arnold, Marcus (Murfreesboro, Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 7)
        - Arrangers’ Publishing Company (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 8)
        - Ashe, Warren and Sonia (Forest Row, Sussex, England) (Box 28, Folder 9)
        - Associated Hospital Service of New York (Box 28, Folder 10)
        - Associated Music Publishers (New York, New York) (Box 28, Folder 11)
        - Associated Musicians of Greater New York (Local 802) (Box 28, Folder 12)
        - Austin Peay State University (Clarksville, Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 13)
        - Bader, Rotraut (Box 28, Folder 14)
          German tax records
        - Baker, David (Bloomington, Indiana) (Box 28, Folder 15)
        - Baltimore Symphony Orchestra (Baltimore, Maryland) (Box 28, Folder 16)
        - Baran, Emile (Decatur, Georgia) (Box 28, Folder 17)
        - Bärenreiter-Verlag (Box 28, Folder 18)
        - Barnes, Christy (Box 28, Folder 19)
        - Barnes, Henry (Dornach, Switzerland) (Box 28, Folder 20)
        - Barrett, Bill, Judy, and Ted (Box 28, Folder 21)
        - Bartok Records (Homosassa, Florida) (Box 28, Folder 22)
        - Bassler, Christel (Box 28, Folder 23)
        - Battle Creek Symphony Orchestra (Battle Creek, Michigan) (Box 28, Folder 24)
        - Belding, Ken and Zoë (Pleasantville, New York) (Box 28, Folder 25)
        - Belmont College (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 26)
        - Bennett, Max (Box 28, Folder 27)
        - Berea College (Berea, Kentucky) (Box 28, Folder 28)
        - Berliner Philharmonisches Orchester (Box 28, Folder 29)
        - Bernstein, Jerry and Cookie (Box 28, Folder 30)
        - Bernstein, Leonard (New York, New York) (Box 28, Folder 31)
        - Editions BIM (Box 28, Folder 32)
        - Blaich, Hiltrud (Stuttgart, Germany), Undated, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 33)
        - Blaich, Hiltrud (Stuttgart, Germany), 1975-1977 (Box 28, Folder 34)
        - Blair School of Music (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 35)
        - Blue Cross Blue Shield (Box 28, Folder 36)
        - Blue Echo Music Inc. (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 37)
        - BooseyS Hawkes, 1966-1979 (Box 28, Folder 38)
        - BooseyS Hawkes, 1980-1996 (Box 28, Folder 39)
        - Bors, Adam and Ada (Eau Claire, Wisconsin) (Box 28, Folder 40)
        - Boston Pops Tour Orchestra (Boston, Massachusetts) (Box 28, Folder 41)
        - Brand, James (Wally) (Box 28, Folder 42)
        - The Brass Press (Box 28, Folder 43)
        - Brevard Music Center (Box 28, Folder 44)
        - Brinker, Bill and Marilyn (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 45)
        - Broadcast Music, Inc. (New York, New York) (Box 28, Folder 46)
        - Brooks, Jim (Pompano Beach, Florida) (Box 28, Folder 47)
        - Broome, P.J. (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 48)
        - Bruesch, Mary Janet (Albuquerque, New Mexico) (Box 28, Folder 49)
        - Buck, Peter (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 28, Folder 50)
        - Buntz, Dick (Box 28, Folder 51)
        - Burgess, Faye (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 52)
        - Burwik, Peter (Box 28, Folder 53)
        - Cagle, Charles (Box 28, Folder 54)
        - California State University—Fullerton (Box 28, Folder 55)
        - Carp, [Gilbert] (Martin, Tennessee) (Box 28, Folder 56)
        - Cavallo-Gulli, Enrica (Bloomington, Indiana) (Box 28, Folder 57)
      - Sketchbooks (Box 29)
        - Citizens’ Bank (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - Clayton, Dan and Barbara (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - Clayton, Dan and Sue (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Cole, Norman (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - Con Edison (New York, New York) (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - Conkling, Leighton (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Connett, Louie (Newton, Mississippi) (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Consulate General of the Federal Republic of Germany (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - Cooke, Charles (Claremont, California) (Box 29, Folder 9)
        - Cox, Bianca (Huntsville, Alabama) (Box 29, Folder 10)
        - Cox, Kenneth (Bloomington, Indiana) (Box 29, Folder 11)
        - Cox, Marsha (San Francisco, California) (Box 29, Folder 12)
        - Crawford, Barnes & Acuff (Cookeville, Tennessee) and McWilliams Realty— (Box 29, Folder 13)
          Content includes legal matters in selling house in Cookeville in 1977-1978
          Also includes household goods descriptive inventory, etc.
        - Cree, Burkert (Box 29, Folder 14)
        - Croom, Freddy (Box 29, Folder 15)
        - Daley, Bill (Box 29, Folder 16)
        - Dallas Symphony Orchestra (Dallas, Texas) (Box 29, Folder 17)
        - Dangel, Hilde (Box 29, Folder 18)
        - Daniels, William (Bill) and Peg, 1950-1951, Jan. (Box 29, Folder 19)
        - Daniels, William (Bill) and Peg, 1951, Sept.-Dec. (Box 29, Folder 20)
        - Daniels, William (Bill) and Peg, 1952-1953 (Box 29, Folder 21)
        - Daniels, William (Bill) and Peg, 1965, 1996, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 22)
        - Davies, Dennis Russell (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 29, Folder 23)
        - Davis, Louise (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 29, Folder 24)
        - Dawson, Jay (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 29, Folder 25)
        - DBVVersicherungen (Box 29, Folder 26)
        - Deerwood, Sammy (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 29, Folder 27)
        - Deighton, Hilda (Spring Valley, New York) (Box 29, Folder 28)
        - Dekker, Isabelle and Hayo (Denver, Colorado) (Box 29, Folder 29)
        - Denney, Katherine (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 29, Folder 30)
        - Dessecker, Brigitte (Box 29, Folder 31)
        - Dews, Tom (Asheville, North Carolina) (Box 29, Folder 32)
        - Deyle, Walter and Uta (Bad Friedrichshall, West Germany), Undated, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 33)
        - Deyle, Walter and Uta (Bad Friedrichshall, West Germany), 1974-1984 (Box 29, Folder 34)
        - Dover Publications, Inc. (Box 29, Folder 35)
        - Doyle, James (Box 29, Folder 36)
        - Drake University (Box 29, Folder 37)
        - Dunnick, Kim and Jane (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 29, Folder 38)
        - Dye, Clifford (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 29, Folder 39)
        - E.?, Ania (Box 29, Folder 40)
        - Ebert, Klaus-Dietrich (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 29, Folder 41)
        - Edmunds, Francis (Forest Row, Sussex), Undated, 1957-1960, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 42)
        - Edmunds, Francis (Forest Row, Sussex), 1975 (Box 29, Folder 43)
        - Edmunds, Francis (Forest Row, Sussex), 1976-1980 (Box 29, Folder 44)
        - Edzard (Box 29, Folder 45)
        - Eelman (Box 29, Folder 46)
        - Egelert, Renate (Tübingen, Germany) (Box 29, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional Folder (Box 30)
        - Einem, Gottfried von (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - Elliott, Francis (Box 30, Folder 2)
        - Emerson (Malibu, California) (Box 30, Folder 3)
        - End, Jack (Rochester, New York) (Box 30, Folder 4)
        - Enix, Margery (Box 30, Folder 5)
        - Enthofer, Adolf (Box 30, Folder 6)
        - Epperson, [?] (Box 30, Folder 7)
        - Ergo Sum Computer, GmbH (Freiburg, Germany) (Box 30, Folder 8)
        - European American Music (Valley Forge, Pennsylvania) (Box 30, Folder 9)
        - Eurythmeum Stuttgart, Undated, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 10)
        - Eurythmeum Stuttgart, 1974-1977, Feb. (Box 30, Folder 11)
        - Eurythmeum Stuttgart, 1977, Mar.-1981 (Box 30, Folder 12)
        - Evangelische Kirchenmusikschule Esslingen (Box 30, Folder 13)
        - Eyle, Felix (New York, New York) (Box 30, Folder 14)
        - Faerber, Jörg (Heilbronn) (Box 30, Folder 15)
        - Farmer, Anette and Guy (Box 30, Folder 16)
        - Fiedler, Arthur (Boston, Massachusetts) (Box 30, Folder 17)
        - Finser, Ruth, Siegfried, and Mark (New York) (Box 30, Folder 18)
        - Carl Fischer Music Publishers (Box 30, Folder 19)
        - Fisk Teachers Agency (Philadelphia, Pennsylvania) (Box 30, Folder 20)
        - Fitzpatrick, William (Box 30, Folder 21)
        - Sam Fox Publishing Company, Undated, 1969-1971 (Box 30, Folder 22)
        - Sam Fox Publishing Company, 1972-1975 (Box 30, Folder 23)
        - Sam Fox Publishing Company, 1976-1980 (Box 30, Folder 24)
        - Sam Fox Publishing Company, 1981-1987 (Box 30, Folder 25)
        - Sam Fox Publishing Company, 1988-1993 (Box 30, Folder 26)
        - Jacques Français Rare Violins, Inc. (New York, New York) (Box 30, Folder 27)
        - Frankfurter Versicherungs-Aktiengesellschaft (Box 30, Folder 28)
        - Freie Waldorfschule Uhlandshöhe (Box 30, Folder 29)
        - Friskin, James and Rebecca (New York, New York) (Box 30, Folder 30)
        - Fruchtman, Eleanor (East Sussex, England) (Box 30, Folder 31)
        - Füssl, Karl Heinz (Box 30, Folder 32)
        - Gerhard, ? (Box 30, Folder 33)
        - Gershevski, Martha (Box 30, Folder 34)
        - Gesellschaft für musikalische Aufführungs- und mechanische Vervielfältigungrechte (GEMA) (Box 30, Folder 35)
        - Goddard, Houston M. (Knoxville, Tennessee) (Box 30, Folder 36)
        - Golden Crest Records, Inc. (Box 30, Folder 37)
        - Goodwin, Rufus (Box 30, Folder 38)
        - Gower, Herschel, Dona, Alison (Leeds, Yorkshire and Nashville, Tennessee), Undated, 1972, 1977-1983 (Box 30, Folder 39)
        - Gower, Herschel, Dona, Alison (Leeds, Yorkshire and Nashville, Tennessee), 1984-1992 (Box 30, Folder 40)
        - Green Meadow School (Spring Valley, New York) (Box 30, Folder 41)
        - Greenhouse, Bernard (Box 30, Folder 42)
        - Gronbach, Karin (Box 30, Folder 43)
        - Grube, Michael (Überlingen/Bodensee, West Germany), Undated, 1972-1975 (Box 30, Folder 44)
        - Grube, Michael (Überlingen/Bodensee, West Germany), 1976-1978, 1983-1989 (Box 30, Folder 45)
        - Guarneri Trio Prague (Box 30, Folder 46)
        - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional (Box 31)
        - H.[?], Carolina (Box 31, Folder 1)
        - Haber, Michael (Box 31, Folder 2)
        - Haidl, lnna[?] (Munich, Germany) (Box 31, Folder 3)
        - Halifax Symphony Society (Halifax, Nova Scotia) (Box 31, Folder 4)
        - Hall, Jim (Box 31, Folder 5)
        - Hanisch, Gucki (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - Hanke, Christiane (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - Harries (Cardiff, Wales) (Box 31, Folder 8)
        - Harrison, Phyllis and Earnest (Box 31, Folder 9)
        - Harriss, Ernest (Martin, Tennessee) (Box 31, Folder 10)
        - Harman, Tissy (Box 31, Folder 11)
        - Harth, Harry and Rainer Kolossa, Rechtsanwälte (Box 31, Folder 12)
        - Harvard University (Cambridge, Massachusetts) (Box 31, Folder 13)
        - Harwell, Coleman (Colie) and Ann (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 31, Folder 14)
        - Hauck, Charles (New York, New York) (Box 31, Folder 15)
        - Heijer, Harriet (Box 31, Folder 16)
        - Henry, Sal [?] (Box 31, Folder 17)
        - Herz, Otto (New York, New York) (Box 31, Folder 18)
        - Hesse, Kate (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 31, Folder 19)
        - Hill, Bob and Debbie (Phoenixville, Pennsylvania) (Box 31, Folder 20)
        - Hirschle (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 31, Folder 21)
        - Hochschule der Künste (Berlin) (Box 31, Folder 22)
        - Hochschule für Musik Würzburg (Box 31, Folder 23)
        - Hodges, Betty (Box 31, Folder 24)
        - Hoepfinger, Mary Alice (Box 31, Folder 25)
        - Hoffmann, Mark (Oxford, Mississippi) (Box 31, Folder 26)
        - Hofmann, Eberhard (Box 31, Folder 27)
        - Holt, Mattie Lou (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 31, Folder 28)
        - Hotubowska, Urszula (Box 31, Folder 29)
        - Houston Symphony Society (Houston, Texas) (Box 31, Folder 30)
        - Hunter, Elizabeth (Box 31, Folder 31)
        - The Instrumentalist (Northfield, Illinois) (Box 31, Folder 32)
        - International Alban Berg Society, Ltd. (Box 31, Folder 33)
        - Internationales Musikfest Stuttgart (Box 31, Folder 34)
        - Irwin, Jana and Jack (Box 31, Folder 35)
        - Jackson Public Schools (Jackson, Mississippi) (Box 31, Folder 36)
        - Jackson Symphony Orchestra (Jackson, Mississippi) (Box 31, Folder 37)
        - Jacksonville University (Jacksonville, Florida) (Box 31, Folder 38)
        - Jennings, Lucile and Gene (Athens, Ohio) (Box 31, Folder 39)
        - Johnston, Warren and Sonia (Box 31, Folder 40)
        - Jordan, Bob and Linda (Box 31, Folder 41)
        - Judson, Richard P. (Chicago, Illinois) (Box 31, Folder 42)
        - Jugend Musiziert, Undated, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 43)
        - Jugend Musiziert, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 44)
        - Jugend Musiziert, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 45)
        - Jugend Musiziert, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 46)
        - Juilliard School of Music (New York, New York) (Box 31, Folder 47)
        - Kansas City Philharmonie (Kansas City, Missouri) (Box 31, Folder 48)
        - Katahn, Enid (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 31, Folder 49)
        - Kendor Music, Inc., Undated, 1975-1978 (Box 31, Folder 50)
        - Kendor Music, Inc., 1979-1995 (Box 31, Folder 51)
        - Kenton, Stan (Hollywood, California) (Box 31, Folder 52)
        - E.C. Kerby, Ltd. (Toronto, Ontario) (Box 31, Folder 53)
        - Kingsway Publications, Ltd. (East Sussex, England) (Box 31, Folder 54)
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional Folder (Box 32)
        - Kless,Yair, Undated, 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
        - Kless,Yair, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - Kless,Yair, 1985-1992 (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - Kneisel Hall (Blue Hill, Maine) (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - Koepf, Herbert and Ursula, Undated, 1966-1975 (Box 32, Folder 5)
        - Koepf, Herbert and Ursula, 1976-2000 (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - Kress, Hanna and Bob (Englewood, New Jersey) (Box 32, Folder 7)
        - Kretz, Harry (Ghent, New York) (Box 32, Folder 8)
        - Kreutz, Arthur and Zoe[?] (Oxford, Mississippi) (Box 32, Folder 9)
        - Krol, Vincenz (Box 32, Folder 10)
        - Krosnick, Joel (Box 32, Folder 11)
        - Krueger, Harold “Harry” (Box 32, Folder 12)
        - Kühn, Isolde and Markus (Oberursel/Taunus, Germa (Box 32, Folder 13)
        - Kuli, Charlotte (Marysville, Tennessee) (Box 32, Folder 14)
        - Lamb, Marvin (Cookeville, Tennessee) (Box 32, Folder 15)
        - Landesgirokasse Stuttgart (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 32, Folder 16)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, Undated (#1) (Box 32, Folder 17)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, Undated (#2) (Box 32, Folder 18)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, Undated (#3) (Box 32, Folder 19)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, Undated (#4) (Box 32, Folder 20)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, Undated (#5) (Box 32, Folder 21)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 22)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 23)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1971-1973 (Box 32, Folder 24)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1974-1976 (Box 32, Folder 25)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 26)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 27)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 28)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 29)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional (Box 33)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - Laney, AI, Irene, and Michael, 1986-1988 (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - Langstroth, Gail (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - Laszloffy, Jerome (Box 33, Folder 4)
        - Lawrence, Steve (New York, New York) (Box 33, Folder 5)
        - Lebowsky, Stanley (Box 33, Folder 6)
        - Lee, Saundra (Box 33, Folder 7)
        - Lehn, Erwin (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 33, Folder 8)
        - Lemonds, Peter (Box 33, Folder 9)
        - John Lewis Associates, Inc. (Box 33, Folder 10)
        - Library of Congress, Copyright Office (Washington, D.C.) (Box 33, Folder 11)
        - Lieberman, Bernie, Liz, Ruth (Oak Ridge, Tennessee), Undated, 1977-1978, Mar. (Box 33, Folder 12)
        - Lieberman, Bernie, Liz, Ruth (Oak Ridge, Tennessee), 1978, May-Dec. (Box 33, Folder 13)
        - Lieberman, Bernie, Liz, Ruth (Oak Ridge, Tennessee), 1979-1981 (Box 33, Folder 14)
        - Lieberman, Bernie, Liz, Ruth (Oak Ridge, Tennessee), 1982-1990 (Box 33, Folder 15)
        - Lindsay, Bryan, Undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
        - Lindsay, Bryan, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 17)
        - Lindsay, Bryan, 1964, Jan.-Apr. (Box 33, Folder 18)
        - Lindsay, Bryan, 1964, May-Jul. (Box 33, Folder 19)
        - Lindsay, Bryan, 1964, Aug.-Oct. (Box 33, Folder 20)
        - Lindsay, Bryan, 1964, Nov.-Dec. (Box 33, Folder 21)
        - Lindsay, Bryan, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 22)
        - Lindsay, Bryan, 1966-1968 (Box 33, Folder 23)
        - Lindsay, Bryan, 1973-1979, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 24)
          Related correspondence under Vanilla Music Publications
        - Louisiana State University (Baton Rouge, Louisiana), Chief correspondents: John Patterson Earnest Harrison Related correspondence under Harrison, Phyllis and Earnest (Box 33, Folder 25)
        - Louisville Orchestra (Louisville, Kentucky) (Box 33, Folder 26)
        - Ludwig Music (Cleveland, Ohio) (Box 33, Folder 27)
        - Lutton Music Personnel Service, Inc. (Chicago, Illinois) (Box 33, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional (Box 34)
        - M., Mary Caroline (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - M.?, Peterand Carol (Box 34, Folder 2)
        - Magg, Fritz (Box 34, Folder 3)
        - Malin, Joseph (New York) (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - Mann, Martina and Christopher (Box 34, Folder 5)
        - Mannes College of Music (New York, New York) (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - Mannheimer Versicherungsgesellschaft (Box 34, Folder 7)
        - Märklin (Box 34, Folder 8)
        - Martin, Fritz (Berlin, Germany) (Box 34, Folder 9)
        - Mason, David and Shiau-Nan (Box 34, Folder 10)
        - Mathis, Johnny (Box 34, Folder 11)
        - Matthiesen (Box 34, Folder 12)
        - Mattke, Jochen (Box 34, Folder 13)
        - Mayfield, George Radford, Mrs. (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 34, Folder 14)
        - McCrory, Martha, Undated, 1968-1972 (Box 34, Folder 15)
        - McCrory, Martha, 1975-1979 (Box 34, Folder 16)
        - McCrory, Martha, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 17)
        - McCrory, Martha, 1982-1988; Associated with the Sewanee Summer Music Center (Box 34, Folder 18)
        - McElhiney, Bill (Box 34, Folder 19)
        - McGhee, Steve (Box 34, Folder 20)
        - McGuffy, Pat (Box 34, Folder 21)
        - Mediaphon Musikproducktion und Verlag, GmbH (Stuttgart, Germany) (Box 34, Folder 22)
        - Memphis City Board of Education (Memphis, Tennessee) (Box 34, Folder 23)
        - Michael Hall School (Sussex, England) (Box 34, Folder 24)
          Chief correspondents: Peter Ramm
          Warren [?]
        - Midtown Properties (New York, New York) (Box 34, Folder 25)
        - Millen, Ellen (Box 34, Folder 26)
        - Mills, Fred (Box 34, Folder 27)
        - Minelli, Charles (Athens, Ohio) (Box 34, Folder 28)
        - Minneapolis Symphony Orchestra (Minneapolis, Minnesota) (Box 34, Folder 29)
        - Miura, Toru (Tokyo, Japan) (Box 34, Folder 30)
        - MJQ Music Inc. (New York, New York) (Box 34, Folder 31)
        - Mollenhauer, Peter and Rosalie, Undated, 1973-1979 (Box 34, Folder 32)
        - Mollenhauer, Peter and Rosalie, 1980-1985 (Box 34, Folder 33)
        - Mollenhauer, Peter and Rosalie, 1986-2002 (Box 34, Folder 34)
        - Montag, Harold and Dot (Lantana, Florida) (Box 34, Folder 35)
        - Moore, Ken (Oberlin, Ohio) (Box 34, Folder 36)
        - Moore, Tom (Box 34, Folder 37)
        - Morrel, John and Maxine (Box 34, Folder 38)
        - Morris, R. Winston, Undated, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 39)
        - Morris, R. Winston, 1980-1986 (Box 34, Folder 40)
        - Morris, R. Winston, 1987-1990 (Box 34, Folder 41)
        - Mt. Olivet Cemetery Company (Nashville, Tennessee) (Box 34, Folder 42)
        - Munkle, Michael (Box 34, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence—Non-Family and Professional (Box 35)
        - Münz (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - Música Sacra in St. Johann (Ludwigsburg, Germany) (Box 35, Folder 2)
        - Musicians’ Protective Association (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - Musikhochschule Lübeck (Box 35, Folder 4)
        - Musikverlag Robert Lienau, Undated, 1985-1988 (Box 35, Folder 5)
        - Musikverlag Robert Lienau, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 6)
        - Muzicka Naklada Export-Import (Zagreb, Yugoslavia) (Box 35, Folder 7)
        - Myslivy, Kathy (Box 35, Folder 8)
        - Nashville Association of Musicians (American Federation of Musicians, Local 257) (Box 35, Folder 9)
        - Nashville Jazz Productions (Dave Converse) (Box 35, Folder 10)
        - Nashville Symphony Orchestra (Box 35, Folder 11)
        - National Orchestral Association (Box 35, Folder 12)
        - National Symphony Orchestra (Washington, D.C.) (Box 35, Folder 13)
        - Nelson, Linda (Box 35, Folder 14)
        - New York, Commissioner of Motor Vehicles (Box 35, Folder 15)
        - New York Philharmonic (New York, New York) (Box 35, Folder 16)
        - New York Telephone Company (Box 35, Folder 17)
        - Nordwall, Trugve, Undated, 1985-1986, Mar. (Box 35, Folder 18)